Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- House no. 12 on Onsi Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; 9959; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref583)
  Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Houses; Architecture; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
- Pharaonic artifacts from Ezbet el-Walda. 9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; 9960; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref584)
  Italian Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Mahmoud Khater Villa. 9 x 13.3 cm, Undated; 9961; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref585)
  Outdoors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Architecture; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- No. 45 Burhan Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9962; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref586)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Houses; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- A boarded up door on AbdelRahman Street. 8.9 x 12.2 cm, Undated; 9963; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref587)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- 26 AbdelRahman Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; 9964; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref588)
  Houses; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Architecture
- View of a street from above, with an Épicerie International in the foreground. 9 x 12 cm, Undated; 9965; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref589)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Shops; Streets/Roads; Postcards; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Restaurants/bars; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings
- House 57 on Al Marsad Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9966; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref590)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Italian Writing
- Helwan's Casino. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9967; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref591)
  Buildings; Casinos; Doors/Entrances; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Entrance gates to a building in Helwan. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9968; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref592)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Houses; Doors/Entrances
- Balcony at 28 Ragheb Street, Helwan. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9969; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref593)
  Houses; Buildings; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- A postcard of a steam train. 9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; 9970; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref594)
  Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Trains; Postcards; Photographic Prints; Transportation
- Postcard of an experimental locomotive equipped with Trevithick heaters. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 9971; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref595)
  Arabic Writing; Trains; French Writing; Postcards; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Transportation; Machines
- House entrance. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1984; 9972; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref596)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Architecture; Photographic Prints
- Gates of a building in Helwan. 13 x 9 cm, 1984; 9973; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref597)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- Bank of Alexandria. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1984; 9974; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref598)
  Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Banks; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Gates on AbdelRahman Street. 13 x 9 cm, 1984; 9975; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref599)
  Doors/Entrances; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- House entrance in Helwan. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9976; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref600)
  Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture
- A wall on Sherif Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9977; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref601)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Graffiti
- View of a house on Riad Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref602)
  Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Buildings
- Entrance of 'Izba AlBajor (Agricultural house). 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9979; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref603)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Doors/Entrances; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings
- Massarah, Helwan. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9980; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref604)
  Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Calligraphy; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Entrance of a building in 'Ezbet AlBahriyyah. 14 x 8.9 cm, 1984; 9981; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref605)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- House entrance. 13 x 9 cm, 1984; 9982; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref606)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Houses; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- House entrance at no. 11 Mansour Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9983; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref607)
  Houses; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances
- House no. 9 entrance on Shabet Street. 9 x 14.1 cm, 1984; 9984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref608)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Houses
- House on Borham Street. 9 x 14.1 cm, 1984; 9985; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref609)
  Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Ezbat Bahrie mosque. 14.1 x 9 cm, 1984; 9986; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref610)
  Photographic Prints; Doors/Entrances; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Mosques; Buildings; Religious Sites
- Muslim cemetery. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref611)
  Cemeteries; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Muslims; Doors/Entrances
- No. 31 Latif Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref612)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Houses; Buildings
- House 42 on Zaki Street. 9 x 13 cm, 1984; 9989; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref613)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Doors/Entrances; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
- House 31 on Latif Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9990; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref614)
  Houses; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Doors/Entrances; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings
- A brick wall behind iron fencing. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9991; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref615)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings
- A building on Azam Mosque Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9992; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref616)
  Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Doors/Entrances; Outdoors; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- No. 62 Mostafta Moraghi Street 13 x 9.1 cm, Undated; 9993; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref617)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt
- Ezbat Al Bahria neighborhood. 14 x 8.9 cm, 1984; 9994; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref618)
  Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Electricity; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Men; Houses; Photographic Prints
- Noor Al Deen villa at 14 Riad Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984; 9995; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref619)
  Buildings; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture
- No. 36 Zaki Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9996; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref620)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Architecture; Doors/Entrances
- No. 23 Ragheb Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9997; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref621)
  Italian Writing; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Helwan, Egypt; Houses
- No. 60 Riad Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9998; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref622)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing
- Boys in front of house no. 5 on Jafar Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 9999; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref623)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Houses; Architecture; Boys; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Buildings
- Entrance of house. 14.1 x 9 cm, 1984; 10000; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref624)
  Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Doors/Entrances; Architecture
- House entrance. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 10001; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref625)
  Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
- House entrance. 14.1 x 9 cm, 1984; 10002; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref626)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Doors/Entrances; Houses; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings
- A dilapidated villa at No. 14 Riad Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10004; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref627)
  Buildings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Houses; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt
- House entrance at no. 22 Khesro Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10005; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref628)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A building on Zaki Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 10006; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref629)
  Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- House entrance at no.67 Mustapha Fahmi Street. 14.1 x 8.9 cm, 1984; 10007; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref630)
  Buildings; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- House at no.62 Azzam Mosque Street. 9 x 14.1 cm, 1984; 10008; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref631)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- A villa on AlMarsad Street with a block of flats in the background. 11.8 x 9 cm, 1984; 10009; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref632)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Houses; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Villa Aquilina at no. 28 on Ragheb Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 10010; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref633)
  Houses; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture
- Mahmoud Khater's Villa. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; 10011; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref634)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- House entrance. 13 x 9 cm, 1984; 10012; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref635)
  Architecture; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing
- A tomb in a Muslim cemetery. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10013; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref636)
  Cemeteries; Architecture; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tombs; Graffiti; Religious Sites
- No. 32 Ragheb Street. 9 x 13 cm, 1984; 10014; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref637)
  Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Houses
- A house in Ezbet Bahrie. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10015; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref638)
  Houses; Architecture; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Electricity; Gelatin Silver Prints
- House on Zaki Street. 13 x 8.9 cm, 1984; 10016; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref639)
  Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- No. 56 Sherif Street (previously San Remo Hotel). 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 10017; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref640)
  Doors/Entrances; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Hotels; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture
- House entrance. 13 x 8.6 cm, Undated; 10018; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref641)
  Houses; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints
- No. 44 Muhammad Sayed Ahmed Street. 14 x 9 cm, Undated; 10019; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref642)
  Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Houses
- No. 32 Ragheb Street. 14 x 9 cm, 1984; 10020; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref643)
  Architecture; Houses; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Transportation; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Building on Ragheb Street. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1984; 10021; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref644)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Cars/Trucks; Architecture; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Transportation
- Detail of a wall in Ezbat Bahrie. 8 x 10.8 cm, 1984; 10022; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref645)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- House on Ismail Kamel Street. 13 x 9 cm, 1984; 10023; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref646)
  Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Architecture
- 12 Azam Mosque Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10024; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref647)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads; Helwan, Egypt
- House on Yousef Street. 8.9 x 13.5 cm, 1984; 10025; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref648)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Palm Trees; Doors/Entrances; Houses
- Helwan sanatorium. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10026; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref649)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Women; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hospitals; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums; Architecture
- Evergreen Hotel. 8.8 x 11.5, Undated; 10027; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref650)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Outdoors; Palm Trees
- Door of house 44 on Mohammed Said Ahmed Street. 9 x 13 cm, 1984; 10028; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref651)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Houses; Italian Writing
- Entrance gates to No.63 Raid Street. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10029; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref652)
  Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Houses; Doors/Entrances; Buildings; Architecture
- Japanese Gardens, Helwan. 8.9 x 14 cm, Undated; 10030; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref653)
  Men; Gardens; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Palm Trees; Outdoors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Parks
- Balcony of house 36 on Street Jaafar. 9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10031; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref654)
  Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses; Architecture
- No. 62 Azam Mosque Street. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, 1984; 10032; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref655)
  Palm Trees; Architecture; Buildings; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- No. 28 Rostom Street. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, Undated; 10033; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref656)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing
- Helwan town center. 9 x 14 cm, 1983; 10034; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref657)
  Electricity; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
- Window of No. 37 Ismail Kamil Street. 9 x 14.1 cm, 1984; 10035; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref658)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Houses; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing
- Greek Orthodox Church on Sherif Street in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1985; 10036; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref659)
  Photographic Prints; Greek Orthodox; Italian Writing; Religious Sites; Architecture; Churches; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- The entrance to the school church. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1984; 10037; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref660)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Churches; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Religious Sites; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
- Helwan Casino door on Mohammed Said Ahmed Street. 8.7 x 13 cm, 1984; 10038; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref661)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Casinos; Doors/Entrances; Buildings
- Detail of a wall at No. 55 Zulfukar Street. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1984; 10039; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref662)
  Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Photographic Prints
- No. 47 Khesro Street. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1984; 10040; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref663)
  Italian Writing; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses
- No. 6 Sobhi Street. 8.9 x 14 cm, 1984; 10041; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref664)
  Architecture; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints
- Entrance of a building in Ezbet Bahria. 9 x 12.2 cm, 1984; 10042; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref665)
  Houses; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Architecture; Doors/Entrances
- Mosque in town, "Ezbet Bahria". 9 x 9.9 cm, 1984; 10043; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref666)
  Mosques; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Street Lamps; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
- Japanese Gardens, Helwan. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, 1984; 10044; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref667)
  Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Parks
- Pharaonic tombs from the first and second dynasties in Ezbet Al Walda. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; 10045; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref668)
  Italian Writing; Tombs; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Countryside/Rural; Deserts; Cemeteries; Religious Sites
- Sulfuric bathhouse. 8.9 x 12.9 cm, 1984; 10046; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref669)
  Taxis; Graffiti; Buildings; Springs; Transportation; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Gelatin Silver Prints; Italian Writing; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Palm Trees; Public Baths; Cars/Trucks